jackofallthreads.co 2016-03-24

# Jackofallthreads.co | Create and Sell High-Quality Unique Apparels

Privacy Policy 

Thank you for visiting our site. The following mentioned below describes how Jack of all Threads collects and   
uses information you provide on our website. The use of service is subject to your acceptance and compliance   
of the following.By using any of our services you agree that you have read, understood and are bound by the   
terms.By violating this agreement in any capacity,you are suject to an immediate removal of your campaign(s)   
possible forfeit of profit(s) and potential suspension or termination of your account. 

Collection of Information:We collect personal information from you such as name,contact information,Billing   
address, Mailing address etc voluntarily submitted by our users.The information provided is solely used for   
order confirmation, response to queries of requested product or service information. This information   
provided is kept secure and is only accessible to authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have   
agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information.You agree that you are the   
owner, or licensee, of all rights associated with any information provided to us (including created or uploaded   
artwork) If you are not the owner, you agree to provide Jack of all Threads with evidence of the permission   
given to you by the owner. 

Cookie/Tracking Technology:Jack of all Threads may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the   
features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type   
and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to Jack of all Threads, and understanding how visitors   
use Jack of all Threads. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be   
collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable   
information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be   
shared with third parties. 

Payment and Security:We provide three methods for you to make a purchase on our site. You can either use   
Order form - fulfil payment by a bank transfer to the account details provided on the form. All information   
provided by this mode of payment is secured and protected Paypal - If you choose to use a third party payment   
option, such as PayPal, to pay for your order, its privacy policy and security practices will apply to your   
information. We encourage you to read that privacy policy before providing your information. 

Cash on Delivery -Shipping details and contact information is provided to our third party vendors that execute   
this service.Sharing of information:In cases of investigation of fraud / misuse of service/content we may share   
information with governmental agencies or other organisations assisting in investigation or prevention. We   
may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law(2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential   
fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place.
